Egmont Arens Papers
Egmont Arens Papers
- Industrial design records
  - Writings
    - Arens, Egmont
      - Articles
        - "The Functions & Responsibilities of an Industrial Designer", 1944 (Box 49)
        - "Pretesting the Post-War Package", 1944 (Box 49)
        - "Low Pressure Molding for Toys & Sporting Goods", 1944 (Box 49)
        - "Air Conditioned Bed & New Bathroom", 1945 (Box 49)
        - "Die Casting for the Modern Package Sealer", 1945 (Box 49)
        - "How's the Readership of Your Package", ca. 1945 (Box 49)
        - "The Industrial Designer Looks At Magazines", 1945 (Box 49)
        - "Lighting to Invite More Customers", ca. 1945 (Box 49)
        - "Design for Maintenance", 1946 (Box 49)
        - "Manhattan Inner Loop Skyway", 1946 (Box 49)
        - "Plastic Film: Syntilie", 1946 (Box 49)
        - "Ten Outstanding Packages of Today", 1946 (Box 49)
        - "Package Redesign Pays", 1947 (Box 49)
        - "Six Basic Elements of Package Redesign", 1947 (Box 50)
        - "Dynamic Design Aids Merchandising", 1947 (Box 50)
        - "Wanted: Fine Color Reproduction on Folding Boxes", 1947 (Box 50)
        - "Cover Package", 1948 (Box 50)
        - "Do You Need a Package Design Counselor?", 1948 (Box 50)
        - "Restaurant Traffic Control Helps to Speed Up Service", 1948 (Box 50)
        - "Make Modern Packages Fast Reading", 1949 (Box 50)
        - "Color Values in Television", 1949 (Box 50)
        - "How To Cash in On Packaging Trends", 1949 (Box 50)
        - "So You Want To Sell Color", 1949 (Box 50)
        - "Type Types Your Package", 1949 (Box 50)
        - "What Plastic Packages Can Do to Freshen Buyer Interest", 1949 (Box 50)
        - "Reinforced Plastics for Furniture", 1949 (Box 50)
        - "Techniques in Fabricating Furniture with Reinforced Plastics", 1949 (Box 50)
        - "White Rose Packages", 1950 (Box 50)
        - "Using Illustration Effectively", 1950 (Box 50)
        - "Prepackaging Fresh Produce Revolutionizes an Industry", 1950 (Box 50)
        - "Drugstore Packaging Goes Super", 1950 (Box 50)
        - "Package Design for Increased Sales", 1950 (Box 50)
        - "Irene Taylor Story", 1950 (Box 50)
        - "New Importance of Good Labels in Modern Merchandising", 1950 (Box 50)
        - "Period Pieces", 1950 (Box 50)
        - "Introduction to Packaging", 1950 (Box 50)
        - "Designer's Outlook", 1950 (Box 50)
        - "How Do You Make Packages Attractive to Children?", 1951 (Box 50)
        - "How a Designer's Name May Be Used as a Guarantee of Quality", 1952 (Box 50)
        - "The Magical Rain Cape", 1952 (Box 50)
        - "Twenty-Five Years of Package Design", 1952 (Box 50)
        - "The Shape of Things", 1952 (Box 50)
        - "Cure for Lazy Trademarks", 1953 (Box 50)
        - "A Designer Looks at the Packaging Show in Chicago for Industry Packaging Trends", 1953 (Box 50)
        - "What's Ahead in Self-Service?", 1953 (Box 50)
        - "A Sale I Will Never Forget...", 1954 (Box 50)
        - "Packaging for Color Television", 1954 (Box 50)
        - "Today's Three A's for Packaging", 1955 (Box 50)
        - "Appraisal of Packaging & Color T.V.", 1955 (Box 50)
        - "Packaging Top Issue in Food Marketing", 1956 (Box 50)
        - "Spotlight on Packaging", 1956 (Box 50)
        - "Yessir, You Can Afford 20,000,000 Salesmen!", 1956 (Box 50)
        - "The Principle Point of Sale Persuader", 1957 (Box 50)
        - "Women's Appetites Dey Modern Packages", 1957 (Box 50)
        - "Package Design for Self-Service Toiletries Market", 1961 (Box 50)
        - "Ideal Bread Package", 1962 (Box 50)
      - Books
        - Consumer Engineering, 1931-1933 (Box 51)
        - Modern Food Marketing, "Stop Traffic With Your Package", 1949 (Box 51)
        - On Industrial Design, background mat., 1958; 2 folders (Box 51)
      - Book reviews
        - Birren, Faber, Creative Color, 1961 (Box 51)
      - Lectures
        - Manuscripts & correspondence
          - On Brand Names, undated (Box 51)
          - On Premiums, undated (Box 51)
          - On Packaging, 1932 (Box 51)
          - "Style in Copywriting", 1932 (Box 51)
          - Remarks at Chicago World's Fair, re: Century of Progress Exhibition, 1933 (Box 51)
          - The Creative Evolution of the Printed Word, 1933 (Box 51)
          - Visual Aspects of Selling, 1934 (Box 51)
          - "See America Streamlined", 1935 (Box 51)
          - On Streamlining, 1935 (Box 51)
          - Roundtable on Industrial Design, 1936 (Box 51)
          - Packages in Uniform, 1936 (Box 51)
          - The Merchandising Hazards of Some Current Packaging Ideas, 1937 (Box 51)
          - Visual Aspects of Streamlining, 1937 (Box 51)
          - Package Engineering, 1937 (Box 51)
          - On Packaging, 1938 (Box 51)
          - New York University Lectures
            - Anatomy of Eye Appeal, undated (Box 52)
            - Correspondence, 1946-1947; undated; 2 folders (Box 52)
          - The Sales Value of Attractive Boxing & Packaging, 1938 (Box 53)
          - Tea Packaging, 1938 (Box 53)
          - Fighting With Color, 1939-1944; undated; 2 folders (Box 53)
          - The Experts Tackle Packaging, 1940 (Box 53)
          - The Functions & Responsibilities of an Industrial Designer, 1944 (Box 53)
          - Designs for Tomorrow, 1944 (Box 53)
          - On A & P Packages, 1945 (Box 53)
          - Low Pressure Molding Comes of Age, 1945 (Box 53)
          - Lecture Trends in the Low Pressure Field, 1946 (Box 53)
          - On Packaging in Terms of Readership, 1948 (Box 53)
          - Finishing & Packaging your Product, 1948 (Box 53)
          - The Psychology of Impulse Buying, 1948 (Box 53)
          - The Redline: A Store Modernization Plan Designed to Stimulate Store Traffic, 1948 (Box 53)
          - How Packaging Can Increase Ice Cream Sales, 1949 (Box 53)
          - Plastics & Premiums--A New Dimension, 1949 (Box 53)
          - Product Merchandising Through Vending Machines, 1949 (Box 53)
          - The Hidden Assets in Your Package, 1949 (Box 53)
          - Package & Label Design, 1949 (Box 53)
          - On Design & Designers, 1950 (Box 53)
          - Canada's Stake in Design, 1950 (Box 53)
          - Package & Product Design, 1950 (Box 53)
          - The Dynamic Use of Color, 1950 (Box 54)
          - Industrial Design & Mass Production, 1950 (Box 54)
          - Package Design, 1950 (Box 54)
          - Wanted: Fine Color Reproduction on Folding Boxes, 1950 (Box 54)
          - The Practice of Industrial Design, 1950 (Box 54)
          - Recent Trends in Label Design, 1950 (Box 54)
          - Use of Color in Product Design, 1950 (Box 54)
          - The Future of Industrial Design, 1950 (Box 54)
          - Packaging for the Mass Market, 1952 (Box 55)
          - Lazy Packages, 1953 (Box 55)
          - Plastics Going High Style, 1953 (Box 55)
          - The Dynamics of Art, 1954 (Box 55)
          - On Produce Packaging, 1954 (Box 55)
          - 7th National Plastics Exposition Remarks, 1956 (Box 55)
          - Significant Trends & Future Developments in Package Design, 1958 (Box 55)
          - Role of Packaging in American Marketing, 1959 (Box 55)
      - Notes and slide captions
        - Art, advertising, undated (Box 56)
        - Art, applied, undated
          - Child, undated (Box 56)
          - Humorous, undated (Box 56)
          - Line, undated (Box 56)
          - Painting, undated (Box 56)
          - Primitive, undated (Box 56)
        - Fashion & costume, undated (Box 56)
        - Household design, undated (Box 56)
        - Housing
          - Architecture, undated (Box 56)
          - Interiors, undated (Box 56)
          - Mobile, undated (Box 56)
        - Industrial design, undated
          - Liege Fair, 1955 (Box 56)
        - Merchandising, undated (Box 56)
        - Packages, undated; 2 folders (Box 56)
        - Photo line, undated (Box 56)
        - Posters, undated (Box 56)
        - Sense of Touch, undated (Box 57)
        - Streamlining in nature, undated (Box 57)
        - Transportation
          - Air, undated (Box 57)
          - Auto, undated (Box 57)
          - Early, undated (Box 57)
          - Marine, undated (Box 57)
          - Railroad, undated (Box 57)
        - Typography, undated (Box 57)
        - Vision, undated (Box 57)
      - Background material
        - Advertising, 1955-1958
          - Creative, 1960- (Box 58)
        - Art Education, 1929-1937 (Box 58)
        - Color, 1931-1951
          - Fighting with Color, 1943 (Box 58)
        - Consumer engineering, 1934-1935 (Box 58)
        - House, movable, undated (Box 58)
        - Industrial design, 1947-1950 (Box 58)
        - Language, speed in, 1934-1950 (Box 58)
        - Mechanizations, Early, 1951 (Box 58)
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 58)
        - Packaging, 1952-1961; undated; 3 folders (Box 58)
        - Photography, 1931-1935 (Box 58)
        - Quotations, 1947-1960; 2 folders (Box 59)
        - Sense of smell, 1935-1950 (Box 59)
        - Streamlining, 1933-1936; 1946
          - Airplanes, 1932-1935; undated (Box 59)
          - Automobiles, 1931-1939 (Box 59)
          - Boats, 1934-1935 (Box 59)
          - Misuse, 1936 (Box 59)
          - Trains, 1933-1934 (Box 60)
          - Type styles, undated (Box 60)
      - Programs, 1947-1958; undated; 2 folders (Box 60)
    - B.B.B.
      - Speech, "Remarks at Exhibition of Modern American Glass", undated (Box 61)
    - Brinkema
      - Article, "The Story of Low Pressure Molding", undated (Box 61)
    - Calkins, E.E.
      - Article, "What Consumption Engineering Really Is", undated (Box 61)
    - Chapman, Dave
      - Doodles, undated (Box 61)
    - Clark, Rene
      - Speech, "On Layout", undated (Box 61)
    - Composing Room, Inc.
      - Article, "About U.S.", 1961 (Box 61)
    - Fitzpatrick, Paul
      - Article, "Why Business Buys Design", 1950 (Box 61)
    - Frank, Betty
      - Article, "Egmont Arens", 1943 (Box 61)
    - Hoffman, Paul
      - Speeches, "On Industrial Design, 1947 (Box 61)
    - Nichols, Dale
      - Article, "Hold that Streamline", undated (Box 61)
    - Shaw, Robert
      - Report, "On Studies of Exhibitions in Europe", undated (Box 61)
    - Sheldon, Roy
      - Articles
        - The Artist Contributes a Merchandising Idea, 1931 (Box 61)
        - Beautiful Bottles, 1931 (Box 61)
        - On Cooperative Merchandising, 1931 (Box 61)
        - Dealing in Futures, 1931 (Box 61)
        - Opportunities Wrapped Up in Combination Packages, 1931 (Box 61)
        - Packages That Make Life Easier for the Consumer, 1931 (Box 61)
        - A Plea for More Convenient Packages, 1931 (Box 61)
        - Psychologically the Depression is Over, 1931 (Box 61)
        - Reputations Lying Idle, 1931 (Box 61)
        - There Ain't No Santa Claus, 1931 (Box 61)
        - On the Wheat Surplus, 1931 (Box 61)
      - Book reviews
        - Tolmer, Mise En Page, 1931 (Box 61)
    - Sims
      - Article, "Ann Page: 4th Generation", undated (Box 61)
    - Smedley, Doree
      - Article, "Fun Ahead", undated (Box 61)
    - Swan, Carroll
      - Article, "How To Tell If Your Package Will Sell", 1948 (Box 61)
    - Wright, Hal
      - Article, "On Holsum Bread", undated (Box 61)
- Miscellany
  - Arens, Camille Davied
    - American Girl file
      - Corres, 1926-1929 (Box 62)
      - Financial records, 1929-1929 (Box 62)
      - Reports, 1927-1928 (Box 62)
    - McCall's file
      - correspondence, reports, copy, 1943-1948 (Box 62)
    - Vogue file
      - Statistics, 1928-1929 (Box 62)
  - Arens, Egmont
    - Address books
      - Bound volume, undated; 2 folders (Box 62)
      - Unbound, 1952 (Box 62)
    - Biographical
      - Clippings, 1936-1955 (Box 62)
      - Introduction & sketches, 1936-1962; undated; 3 folders (Box 62)
      - University of New Mexico, 1910-1964 (Box 62)
    - Diaries
      - Bound, 1901-1914; undated; 5 folders (Box 62)
      - Unbound notes, 1922-1923 (Box 63)
    - Ephemera
      - Cartoons, sketches, undated (Box 63)
      - Christmas cards, 1939-1963
        - Of others, undated (Box 63)
      - Clippings, 1921-1939 (Box 63)
      - Hobbies, 1941-1943; undated; 2 folders (Box 63)
      - Post cards, undated; 3 folders (Box 63)
      - Wedding announcements, 1914 (Box 63)
    - Financial records
      - Bills & receipts, 1951-1956; 1916; 2 folders (Box 63)
      - Credit cards, 1961 (Box 64)
      - Safe deposit box, 1952 (Box 64)
      - Tax records
        - New York State, 1929-1952
        - New York State Adjustments, 1939-1954 (Box 64)
        - United States, 1929-1952 (Box 64)
    - Kent, Rockwell, 1932-1937; undated; photo., handwritten notes, clippings (Box 64)
    - Landscape layout, Huntington, L.I., 1953 (Box 64)
    - Legal records
      - Agreements, 1956-1957 (Box 64)
      - Bill of Sale, 1923 (Box 64)
      - Divorce, 1923; 1952 (Box 64)
      - I.D. cards & passports, 1949-1961 (Box 64)
      - Lawsuit, 1926 (Box 64)
      - Partnership, 1905 (Box 64)
      - Security clearance, 1950-1951 (Box 64)
      - Will, 1947 (Box 64)
    - Medical records
      - Miscellaneous, 1933-1960 (Box 65)
      - Electrocardiograms & X-rays, 1946-1962 (Box 65)
    - Photographs & negatives
      - Arens, Egmont, undated; 3 folders (Box 65)
      - Book label, undated (Box 65)
      - Camping trips, 1904; undated (Box 65)
      - Chest of drawers, undated (Box 65)
      - Chickens, undated (Box 65)
      - Desk & chair, undated (Box 66)
      - "Ellenwood", undated (Box 66)
      - Europe, undated (Box 66)
      - Gorodnitzky, Beatrice, undated (Box 66)
      - Greenwich Village Friends, 1952-1954; 1920; 1 folder (Box 66)
      - House, Southport, Connecticut, ca. 1940 (Box 66)
      - "Lake Nebo:, 1901-1902 (Box 67)
      - Landscape, New Mexico, undated (Box 67)
      - "Loomis San", undated (Box 67)
      - Oregon, undated (Box 67)
      - Personal
        - RESTRICTED, undated; 1 folder (Box 66)
        - Slides, (box 1), 1943-1950 (Box 66)
        - Slides, (box 2), 1952-1954 (Box 67)
      - "Pirates", undated (Box 68)
      - "Portraits of the Past from Greenwich Village", undated (Box 68)
      - Rex Stout, undated (Box 68)
      - Stacking Hay, undated (Box 68)
      - Statues, undated (Box 68)
      - University of New Mexico, undated (Box 68)
      - Wagon & Team, undated (Box 68)
      - World's Fair, 1939 (Box 68)
      - Unidentified, undated; 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Sketches
      - Flo Walderman, undated (Box 68)
    - Sports
      - Boating
        - Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 68)
        - correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 68)
        - correspondence, 1954-1965; 2 folders (Box 69)
    - Travel, 1949 (Box 69)
  - Arens, Emma Huegal
    - Estate, 1936 (Box 69)
    - Photographs & negatives, undated (Box 69)
  - Arens, Franz Xavier
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 69)
    - Scrapbook: "The Hermit's Letters", 1878 (Box 70)
  - Arens, Josephine Bell
    - Legal records, will, 1923 (Box 69)
    - Photographs & negatives, undated (Box 69)
  - Arens, Mathilde Zwilling
    - Miscellaneous, 1951 (Box 69)
    - Paul Sayres Company, Inc. File, 1949-1951; 2 folders (Box 69)
    - Public Relations File, 1949-1952; 2 folders (Box 69)
  - Arens, Patricia
    - Ephemera
      - Miscellany, undated (Box 71)
      - Clippings, undated (Box 71)
    - Photographs & negatives, 1945; undated (Box 71)
  - Arens, Ralph Waldo
    - Financial records
      - Sale of apples, 1941-1942 (Box 71)
  - Arens Ruth Chrisman?
    - Photographs & negatives, undated (Box 71)
  - Arens Family
    - Genealogical material, 1939-1963 (Box 71)
  - Egts, J. Marie
    - Miscellany, 1956 (Box 71)
    - Financial records, 1956-1957 (Box 71)
    - Legal records, 1928-1957 (Box 71)
- Organization records
  - American Institute of Graphic Art, 1955-1956; correspondence, notes (Box 72)
  - Gaslight Club, 1958-1961; correspondence, notes (Box 72)
  - Inter-Society Color Council
    - By-laws, 1944-1954 (Box 72)
    - correspondence, 1948-1963; 3 folders (Box 72)
    - Election ballot, 1952-1962 (Box 72)
    - Membership lists, 1952-1963 (Box 72)
    - Report, undated (Box 72)
    - Minutes, 1948-1957 (Box 73)
    - News letters, 1954-1963; 3 folders (Box 73)
    - Programs, 1952-1962 (Box 73)
    - Publicity material, 1958; undated (Box 73)
    - Report, 1949-1960; 1957; 2 folders (Box 74)
  - Labor Manufacturers' National Association, 1950-1951; correspondence, pr. mat. (Box 74)
  - Lithographers' National Association, Inc., 1956; correspondence, pr. mat. (Box 74)
  - National American Wholesale Grocers Association Inc.
    - correspondence, 1952 (Box 74)
    - Management forum, 1952 (Box 74)
  - National Automatic Merchandising Association, 1949; 1955 (Box 74)
  - Package Designers' Council
    - Awards & special exhibits, 1962 (Box 74)
    - By-laws, 1958 (Box 74)
    - Certificate of Membership, 1961 (Box 74)
    - Conference on Packaging, 1957 (Box 74)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1963 (Box 75)
    - Minutes, 1958-1963 (Box 75)
    - Programs, 1957 (Box 75)
    - Publicity material, 1953-1955 (Box 75)
    - Report, 1956 (Box 75)
  - Package Research Conference, proceedings, 1957 (Box 75)
  - Packaging Institute, Inc.
    - Addresses, 1955 (Box 75)
    - Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 75)
  - Peoples Symphony Concert
    - Bank account, 1943-1944 (Box 75)
    - By-laws, 1951 (Box 75)
    - Correspondence, 1931-1961; 2 folders (Box 75)
    - Minutes, 1936-1964 (Box 75)
    - Programs, 1906-1957 (Box 75)
    - Publicity material, 1900-1965 (Box 75)
    - Report, 1932-1951 (Box 75)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1952-1961; 9 folders (Box 76)
  - Pratt Institute, 1953; correspondence, brochure (Box 76)
  - Produce Packaging Association, 1954; misc, conf. mat. (Box 76)
  - The Sales Executive Club of New York, 1960-1952 (Box 76)
  - Society of Industrial Designers
    - Addresses, 1959-1962 (Box 76)
    - Book: Industrial Design in America, 1946 (Box 76)
    - By-laws, 1957-1961 (Box 76)
    - Code of Practice, undated (Box 76)
    - Correspondence, 1946-1963; 4 folders (Box 77)
    - List of members, 1952-1963 (Box 77)
    - Minutes of early organization meetings, 1944-1946 (Box 77)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 78)
    - Newsletters, 1954-1964; 2 folders (Box 78)
    - Photographs, 1949 (Box 78)
    - Programs, undated (Box 78)
    - Publicity material, undated (Box 78)
    - Report, 1962; undated (Box 78)
    - Standards, services listings, undated (Box 78)
  - Society of Industrial Engineers
    - Agenda, first meeting, 1945 (Box 79)
    - By-laws, 1939 (Box 79)
    - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 79)
    - Directory, 1948 (Box 79)
    - Statement, 1945 (Box 79)
  - Society of Plastics Engineers, 1955; correspondence, notes (Box 79)
  - Society of the Plastics Industry, Inc.
    - Correspondence, 1949-1956 (Box 79)
    - Informative labeling committee, 1950-1952 (Box 79)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 79)
    - Publicity material, 1949-1956 (Box 79)
- Publication records
  - Conde Nast Publications
    - Promotional materials
      - Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 80)
      - Designed by Egmont Arens, 1921 (Box 80)
    - Vanity Fair, 1929; 1934,; undated; correspondence, handwritten notes (Box 80)
  - Flying Stag Press
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 80)
    - Books
      - Brodsky, Horace, A Portfolio of Linoleum Cuts, New York, No. 6 of 100, signed by the artist, 1920; 1920; Transferred to Rare Books for separate cataloging; please refer to
      - Casanova, Giovanni Jacopo, Memoirs. 12 volumes, New York: Aventuros, 1925
        - Miscellaneous
          - Art work for bindings, 1925 (Box 80)
          - Illustrations by Rockwell Kent, 1925 (Box 80)
          - Legal papers and cost report, 1925 (Box 80)
          - Photographs, 1925 (Box 80)
          - Promotional material, 1925 (Box 80)
        - Draft, Introduction by Arthur Symons ts. rev., 1925 (Box 80)
        - Page proofs, rev., 1925
          - Volume 1 (Box 80)
          - Volumes 2-5 (Box 81)
          - Volumes 6-9 (Box 82)
          - Volumes 10-12 (Box 83)
        - Published materials, Volumes 1-12, Transferred to Rare Books for separate cataloging; please refer to
      - Cronyn, George, Sandbar Queen. Flying Stag Plays, No. 1, 1918; Transferred to Rare Books for separate cataloging; please refer to
      - De La Mer, Alice, Paulet Thevanaz, privately printed, 1922; Transferred to Rare Books for separate cataloging; please refer to
      - Dell, Floyd, The Angel Intrudes, Flying Stag Plays, No. 3, New York, 1918; Transferred to Rare Books for separate cataloging; please refer to
    - Catalogs of Art Exhibits, 1919-1922 (Box 84)
    - Correspondence, 1920-1960; undated; 17 folders (Box 84)
    - Periodicals
      - Playboy
        - Nos. 1-9, 1919-1924; Transferred to Rare Books for separate cataloging; please refer to
        - Fragments, undated; Transferred to Rare Books for separate cataloging; please refer to
        - Subscription list, undated (Box 85)
    - Posters, undated (Box 85)
    - Samples of Work, 1920-1925; undated (Box 85)
  - Liberty Magazine
    - Correspondence, 1935; undated (Box 85)
    - Cover blueprints, 1935 (Box 85)
    - Cover ideas, 1935 (Box 85)
    - Page layout, 1935; undated; 2 folders (Box 85)
- Writings
  - Arens, Egmont H.
    - Articles
      - "British Labor Walks Out," New Masses, Vol. 1, No. 2, 1926 (Box 85)
      - Hugo Gellert exhibition catalog, 1923 (Box 85)
      - "John Carroll: Passionate Young Modern," Creative Art, Vol. 1, No. 2, 1927 (Box 85)
    - Poems
      - "Blind," Pagan, Vol. 2, Nos. 3&4, 1917 (Box 85)
      - "The Cool of the Night," Collier's, Vol. 5, No. 99, 1915 (Box 85)
      - "Fear and Love," Pagan, Vol 2, No. 2, 1917 (Box 85)
      - "Great and Moving Days,", The Conservator, Vol. 29, No. 3, 1918 (Box 85)
      - "Love and Revolution," The Conservator, Vol. 28, No. 1, 1917 (Box 85)
      - "Our Walnut Tree," and "Gay Moon," The Quill, Vol. 2, No. 2, 1918; Transferred to Rare Books for separate cataloging; please refer to
      - "Remembrance," Pagan, Vol. 3, No. 9, 1918 (Box 86)
      - "Twenty Blocks" and other poems, A Pagan Anthology, New York: Pagan Publishing Company, ca. 1918; Transferred to Rare Books for separate cataloging; please refer to
      - Fragments and unbound poems and notes, undated (Box 86)
  - Cumming, Edward
    - Short Stories, "That Spring Miss Lou and I", undated (Box 86)
  - Doro, Edward
    - Short Stories, "Parisian Interlude", undated (Box 86)